I try to help as best it goes into the last.
He has a little stressful ... hehehe.
He still has a lot and still do.
-What is your task today?
It will be to help him with small things.
Then he gets to polish and polish what he is good at.
It's a switch.
There are 2 ink here and here the cables are switched on.
And screws ate with them hear the screws.
Then you stop in this ...
So it sits there ... when you turn it out.
He is good at this Sven.
It will go well.
It is certainly something that needs to be fixed, but it will go well.
Tjena, welcome!
Good today's!
Here are the guys who have balanced the entire engine package.
Crankshafts, drove yes the rub ...
Now we see if it works.
-Had you managed to do this yourself?
I probably hadn't been able to.
It probably takes some letters to cope with it.
-Do you have any vehicles yourself?
Well I have some mustangs standing.
Sven can you open the door?
So we get some air.
We may need it.
Finally!
-Are you happy?
Now I'm happy.
It was good ride in the engine when it got hot.
Ah but it needs to be run in before piston rings and everything has settled.
It is noticeable that it leaks a little.
Now it will work.
Now it is just driving on so you get ready for Elmia.
There is only a little polishing left.
Always exciting.
Absolutely superb.
Yes it was something new.
Yes with such simple means.
You have witnessed as no one else has seen.
I haven't seen any straight 12A.
Definitely no one with offset ignition.
-Can he approve then?
Oh.
With praise!
Then we come to the look but there it is the taste like the back.
It was probably a sense that I would have a crane here.
If 10 points are perfect then it's almost a 9a.
You can expect a little leakage.
That I must have choke ... yes you could have thought of it.
Other I think the engine went well.
And then the engine is not yet run.
I am satisfied, really satisfied.
It will be fun to test drive then.
-So this was the thing to fix?
Yep, this is the water leakage.
Are you doing it or can you blame someone?
That's myself.
It is a very own construction.
Unfortunately, I can't blame anyone else.